<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetadata xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <Name>Inventory Tweaks</Name>
    <Author>theit8514</Author>
    <Version>0.4.5</Version>
    <Description><![CDATA[[h1]Inventory Tweaks[/h1]
        This mod is designed to improve the inventory management aspect of Stationeers.
        [h2]Requirements[/h2]
        WARNING: This is a StationeersLaunchPad Plugin Mod. It requires BepInEx to be installed with the StationeersLaunchPad plugin.
        See: https://github.com/StationeersLaunchPad/StationeersLaunchPad
        Detailed installation instructions available here: https://github.com/theit8514/Stationeers-InventoryTweaks#installation-steam-workshop
        [h2]Features[/h2]
        * Combine items into existing stacks when moving via Smart Stow (default G)
        * Add keybind for hitting "Next" on your current active item (for example, the Advanced Tablet)
        * Fixes weird gaps between inventory windows
        * Fixes tracking of original slots so that items return to their proper place via Smart Stow.
        * Ability to lock slots to an item type (e.g. Hand Drill, Cable Coil, etc.). Hover over the slot using Alt and press keybind to lock/unlock.
        * Override Inventory Select keybind to allow swapping when Invalid slot selected (e.g. trying to swap non-tool into a tool slot)
        [h2]License[/h2]
        This mod is open source and available from [url=https://github.com/theit8514/Stationeers-InventoryTweaks]theit8514/Stationeers-InventoryTweaks[/url] on GitHub
    ]]></Description>
    <ChangeLog><![CDATA[
        0.4.5:
        - Fixed new save not creating directory structure

        0.4.4:
        - Fixed NRE with Inventory Select on an empty slot of a type not matching the item type

        0.4.3:
        - Added config option for overriding Inventory Select keybind for Invalid slots (e.g. trying to swap non-tool into a tool slot)
        - Fixed stowing item currently under construction.
        - Fixed key conflict message.
        - Fixed migration when file already exists.

        0.4.2:
        - Fixed Stationeers crashes when mod is uninstalled. This change requires InventoryTweaks save data to be migrated.
        - Fixed duplicate harmony patching if installed multiple times.
        
        0.4.1:
        - Published to Steam Workshop

        0.4.0:
        - Updated for Stationeers "Biggest Update Ever"
        - Fixed Open Slot detection for tools, adding items with hash "None"
        - Updated to new save format
        - Fixed lock slots being filled with Smart Stow
    ]]></ChangeLog>
    <WorkshopHandle>3573053238</WorkshopHandle>
    <Tags />
    <Dependencies />
    <LoadBefore />
    <LoadAfter />
    <InGameDescription xsi:nil="true" />
</ModMetadata>